<Publish>
	<ModId Value="148238" />
	<DisplayName Value="Subdivisions" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Create districts that follow your networks." />
	<LongDescription>
Subdivisions creates districts whose boundaries follow your networks instead of being painted on freehand. Drop a few points around an area and the tool traces the boundary along the networks between them, so each district hugs your layout cleanly. It is handy for splitting a city into neighborhoods, planning zoning block by block, or laying out service areas that line up with your streets, rail, and paths.

## How to use
- Activate the tool from its button in the top-left of the screen.
- Left-click to drop boundary points around a block or neighborhood.
- Click the first point again to close the ring and create the district.
- Right-click to remove the last point.

A live preview and color-coded markers show the shape as you build it, so you can see exactly where each point will land.

## Snapping
Points snap to:
- Networks of any kind - roads, rail, and pedestrian paths (intersections are preferred when you click near one)
- Existing district boundaries
- Map-tile borders

## Tracing
The boundary follows your networks along the shortest route between points, including elevated and tunnel sections. When two neighboring points are on different kinds of network, they are joined with a straight line instead. Utility lines such as power and water are ignored. Existing districts stay visible on the map while the tool is active.

## Recommended Mods
[Anarchy](https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/74604/Windows) by yenyang is not required, but it is handy to have available while creating districts.
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screen1.jpg" />
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.1.0" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/EjafiSoftware/Subdivisions" />
	<ChangeLog>
## Version 1.0.1

* Fixed valid network-following boundaries being flattened into straight lines.
* Switched to A* for faster, more direct boundary tracing.

## Version 1.0.0

* Initial release to Github (no code changes)

## Version 0.2.4

* Update for patch 1.6.0f1

## Version 0.2.3

* Fixed boundaries crossing themselves when two points sat on different network types (such as a road and a rail line).
* Fixed districts collapsing into a thin sliver when two points were on the same road loop; the boundary now wraps the block between them.
* Faster boundary tracing across large road networks.

## Version 0.2.2

* Restored the live district preview while placing boundary points.
* The tool no longer creates a district when the closed ring is invalid.

## Version 0.2.1

* Fixed the tool committing a district every frame while hovering; the district is now created only when the boundary ring is closed.
* Removed unused settings that remained from a legacy version.

## Version 0.2.0

* First public beta release.
	</ChangeLog>

	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
